[
  {
    "name": "Beverly Hazzard",
    "mrn": "2009527",
    "chief_complaint": "HEADACHE",
    "ehr": {
      "dob": "01/15/1990", "gender": "F", "weight": "192", "height": "165", "age": "27"
    },
    "findings": {
      "vitals": [
          {"question": "TEMP", "answer": "37"},
          {"question": "SBP", "answer": "110"},
          {"question": "DBP", "answer": "74"},
          {"question": "RESP_RATE", "answer": "35"},
          {"question": "PULSE", "answer": "98"},
          {"question": "CAPILLARY_REFILL", "answer": "NORMAL"},
          {"question": "URINE_OUTPUT", "answer": "75"},
          {"question": "ALTERED_LOC", "answer": "NO"}
      ],
      "lab_results": [
        {"question": "WBC", "answer": "12.5"}
      ],
      "problems": [
        {"question": "UTI", "answer": "YES"},
        {"question": "BIPOLAR", "answer": "YES"},
        {"question": "HYPERTENSION", "answer": "NO"}
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "name": "Mary Hernandez",
    "mrn": "2009528",
    "chief_complaint": "",
    "ehr": {
      "dob": "05/10/1939", "gender": "F", "weight": "165", "height": "160", "age": "78"
    },
    "findings": {
      "vitals": [
          {"question": "TEMP", "answer": "38"},
          {"question": "SBP", "answer": "86"},
          {"question": "DBP", "answer": "48"},
          {"question": "RESP_RATE", "answer": "20"},
          {"question": "PULSE", "answer": "115"},
          {"question": "PULSE_OX", "answer": "91"},
          {"question": "NPO", "answer": "NO"},
          {"question": "ALTERED_LOC", "answer": "YES"}
      ],
      "lab_results": [],
      "problems": [
        {"question": "DIABETESII", "answer": "YES"},
        {"question": "HYPERTENSION", "answer": "YES"}
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "name": "Susan Shade",
    "mrn": "2009529",
    "chief_complaint": "",
    "ehr": {
      "dob": "06/11/1973", "gender": "F", "weight": "110", "height": "158", "age": "43"
    },
    "findings": {
      "vitals": [
          {"question": "TEMP", "answer": "37"},
          {"question": "SBP", "answer": "105"},
          {"question": "DBP", "answer": "70"},
          {"question": "RESP_RATE", "answer": "25"},
          {"question": "NPO", "answer": "NO"},
          {"question": "ALTERED_LOC", "answer": "NO"}
      ],
      "lab_results": [
        {"question": "K", "answer": "3.3"},
        {"question": "Na", "answer": "125"}
      ],
      "problems": []
    }
  },
  {
    "name": "Mitchell Matthews",
    "mrn": "2009530",
    "chief_complaint": "COUGH",
    "ehr": {
      "dob": "10/22/1955", "gender": "M", "weight": "187", "height": "172", "age": "61"
    },
    "findings": {
      "vitals": [
          {"question": "TEMP", "answer": "38"},
          {"question": "SBP", "answer": "125"},
          {"question": "DBP", "answer": "87"},
          {"question": "RESP_RATE", "answer": "30"},
          {"question": "PULSE", "answer": "95"},
          {"question": "NPO", "answer": "YES"},
          {"question": "ALTERED_LOC", "answer": "NO"}
      ],
      "lab_results": [
        {"question": "GLUCOSE", "answer": "245"}
      ],
      "problems": [
        {"question": "DIABETESII", "answer": "YES"},
        {"question": "HYPERTENSION", "answer": "YES"}
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "name": "Angela Williams",
    "mrn": "2009531",
    "chief_complaint": "HEADACHE",
    "ehr": {
      "dob": "08/05/1949", "gender": "F", "weight": "99", "height": "160", "age": "67"
    },
    "findings": {
      "vitals": [
          {"question": "TEMP", "answer": "37"},
          {"question": "SBP", "answer": "110"},
          {"question": "DBP", "answer": "65"},
          {"question": "RESP_RATE", "answer": "24"},
          {"question": "PULSE", "answer": "120"},
          {"question": "NPO", "answer": "YES"},
          {"question": "O2_REQUIREMENT", "answer": "YES"},
          {"question": "ALTERED_LOC", "answer": "YES"}
      ],
      "lab_results": [],
      "problems": [
        {"question": "HEART_FAILURE", "answer": "YES"}
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "name": "James Gorham",
    "mrn": "2009532",
    "chief_complaint": "HEADACHE",
    "ehr": {
      "dob": "10/05/1955", "gender": "M", "weight": "160", "height": "165", "age": "61"
    },
    "findings": {
      "vitals": [
          {"question": "TEMP", "answer": "37"},
          {"question": "SBP", "answer": "110"},
          {"question": "DBP", "answer": "65"},
          {"question": "PULSE", "answer": "120"},
          {"question": "RESP_RATE", "answer": "24"},
          {"question": "NPO", "answer": "YES"},
          {"question": "O2_REQUIREMENT", "answer": "YES"},
          {"question": "ALTERED_LOC", "answer": "YES"}
      ],
      "lab_results": [
        {"question": "CREATININE", "answer": "2.3"}
      ],
      "problems": [
        {"question": "HEART_FAILURE", "answer": "NO"}
      ]
    }
  }
]